A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.40 (A2015) FA761
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2015.037: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-2015; 2000-2014; 9.2 Cubic Feet Seven standard record storage boxes, R4447-R4453.
  - SRC, 2012-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 SRC 111 - OCEANA - "SAVE THE OCEANS - FEED THE WORLD" PROJECT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 112 - ACCENTURE LLP - EXTERNAL SCAN ISSUE AREA RESEARCH, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
- AC.2015.060: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2000-2014; AC_2015_060; 7.89 Cubic Feet Six standard record storage boxes, R4454-R4459.
  - Transforming Health Systems (THS), 2010-2014; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2012 THS 301 - HEALTH PARTNERS INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - MINING PPPs TO STRENGTHEN HEALTH SYSTEMS, 2012-2013 (Box R4454)
    - 2012 THS 302 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - HEALTH SYSTEMS IN THE GLOBAL SOUTH, 2010-2014; 2 folders (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 308 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - GLOBAL HEALTH DIPLOMACY NETWORK IN ASIA, 2010-2014 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 309 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - PRIVATE SECTOR IN HEALTH RESEARCH ASSOCIATION, 2012-2014 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 314 - ASIAN COMMUNITY HEALTH ACTION NETWORK (INDIA) - PEOPLE'S HEALTH ASSEMBLY 2012 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 317 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - HEALTH POLICIES IN AFRICA, SE ASIA AND WESTERN PACIFIC, 2012-2013 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 322 - PEKING UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - 2ND GLOBAL SYMPOSIUM ON HEALTH SYSTEM RESEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 326 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH POLICY PROGRAM (THAILAND) - 7TH ASIA PACIFIC ACTION ALLIANCE ON HUMAN RESOURCES FOR HEALTH CONFERENCE, 2012-2013 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 329 - PARTNERS IN HEALTH - OPENMRS PRIMARY HEALTH CARE MODULES IN RWANDA, 2010-2014 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 331 - FACULTAD LATINO AMERICANA DE CIENCIAS SOCIALES (CHILE) - UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE AND INFORMAL WORKERS IN LATIN AMERICA, 2012-2013 (Box R4455)
    - 2012 THS 332 - ST. MICHAEL'S HOSPITAL (CANADA) - MONITORING AND EVALUATION OF RF TRANSFORMING HEALTH SYSTEMS INITIATIVE, 2012-2013 (Box R4456)
  - TRA, 1981-2014; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 TRA 302 - GAMALIEL FOUNDATION - TRANSPORTATION EQUITY NETWORK, 2010-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 303 - BUILDING AMERICA'S FUTURE EDUCATIONAL FUND - NATIONAL POLL ON INVESTMENTS IN TRANSPORTATION INFRASTRUCTURE AND REFORM, 2011-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 305 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST - ONE REGION FUNDERS COLLABORATIVE, 2010-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 307 - LIVABLE COMMUNITIES COALITION - ATLANTA REGION TRANSIT REVENUE CAMPAIGN, 2010-2012 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 308 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - DEVELOP A ROBUST GOLD-STANDARD BUS RAPID TRANSIT SYSTEM, 2011-2012 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 310 - POLICY LINK - BC CONFERENCE - ECONOMIC GROWTH AND EQUITY, 2011-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 311 - FUNDERS' NETWORK FOR SMART GROWTH AND LIVABLE COMMUNITIES - STRENGTHEN PHILANTHROPIC SUPPORT OF TRANSPORTATION, 2008-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 312 - SAFE STREETS FUND, INC. - ECONOMIC IMPACT STUDY OF NYC STREET IMPROVEMENTS, 2011-2013 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 313 - RESOURCES LEGACY FUND - REDUCTION OF GREENHOUSE GAS EMISSIONS IN CALIFORNIA, 2010-2014 (Box R4456)
    - 2012 TRA 315 - UNITED STATES PUBLIC INTEREST RESEARCH GROUP EDUCATION FUND, INC. - TRANSPORTATION FOR THE NEXT GENERATION PROJECT, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 316 - RAIL-VOLUTION - "BUILDING LIVABLE COMMUNITIES WITH TRANSIT" CONFERENCE, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 317 - NEW YORK PUBLIC RADIO - TRANSPORTATION REPORTER TRAINING, 2012-2013 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 318 - TIDES CENTER - THE BRIDGES INITIATIVE - WINNING THE GENERATIONAL SHIFT, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 319 - REGIONAL PLAN ASSOCIATION - RAIL TRANSPORTATION INVESTMENTS ACROSS THE NEW YORK AND NEW JERSEY REGION, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 321 - CENTER FOR NEIGHBORHOOD TECHNOLOGY - HOUSING AND TRANSPORTATION AFFORDABILITY INDEX, 2008-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 322 - TIDES FOUNDATION - CONVERGENCE PARTNERSHIP - COLLABORATION ON PLACE, HEALTH AND TRANSPORTATION, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 323 - SMART GROWTH AMERICA - TRANSPORTATION FOR AMERICA CAMPAIGN, 2012-2014 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 324 - LEADERSHIP CONFERENCE ON CIVIL RIGHTS EDUCATION FUND - LEADING THE SOCIAL EQUITY CAUCUS ON TRANSPORTATION REFORM, 2011-2013 (Box R4459)
    - 2012 TRA 325 - ENVIRONMENTAL LAW AND POLICY CENTER - SUSTAINABLE TRANSPORTATION AND LAND USE IN THE MIDWEST, 2009-2014 (Box R4459)
  - Food Security (FS), 2010-2012; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2005 FS 060 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRONOMIC RESEARCH - MAIZE BREEDING PROGRAM, 2000-2012 (Box R4459)
  - CAB, 2007-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 CAB 303 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF RWANDA - PEDAGOGY AND MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS, 2007-2014 (Box R4459)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS - Videos (Box R4457)
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS - Videos (Box R4458)